Are you here to hire an escort?
No.
Looking at your physique,
are you here to apply for an escort?
Is Su Yuejiao here?
She's busy.
You can tell me.
Who are you?
Why did he leave?
Why are people so weird lately?
Where's your boss?
He went out to escort goods.
He hasn't come back yet.
Why didn't you go with him?
Today is the day of the contest.
The boss asked me to stay here to help Cheng Qi.
Where's Cheng Qi?
I don't know.
Go find him.
Young Master Cheng
Wake up.
Get up.
The contest is about to start.
Why are you here?
What time is it now?
The contest is about to start.
Oh, no.
Hurry up.
Go, go, go.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Being late
is against the rules.
Master Su,
this round,
Dabao should be the winner, right?
We escort people,
and we value punctuality and keeping promises.
This round,
Dabao wins.
Round one,
Zhen Dabao wins.
No way,
This round doesn't count.
Rules are rules.
How can you just make a mess like this?
Grandpa,
he...
He must've just arrived and slept poorly.
so he was late.
Since you've married into the Su family,
you must follow the Su family's rules.
Next round,
we'll compete in business strategies.
We often need to check the goods
and calculate the money
we should get.
Here's the question.
There are chickens and rabbits in a cage.
There are 35 heads.
There are 94 feet.
How many
chickens and rabbits are there?
Grandfather,
this question is too difficult.
Cheng Qi is just a scholar.
He's not good at arithmetic.
Dad.
Jiaojiao has a point.
Even I, who am good at business,
feel a bit challenged.
These two
definitely can't answer it.
Grandfather.
Cheng Qi
wants to try.
Dabao,
do you understand?
Dabao can figure it out with candies.
Alright.
Let's start the game.
Five candies
minus three candies
equals eight candies.
Okay,
both sides,
reveal your answers simultaneously.
Lishi,
who's the winner?
I dare not say
whether Cheng Qi is right.
But
Dabao's answer
is definitely wrong.
The answer of Cheng Qi,
my husband,
is correct.
Why is his answer correct?
What if he just guessed?
He should at least
explain something.
If we assume there are 35 chickens,
that would be 70 legs.
But in reality,
there are 94 legs.
The 24 missing legs
come from the rabbits mistaken as chickens.
So we should deduct 12 rabbits from the assumed 35 chickens.
There are 23 chickens
in total.
As for the rabbits,
there are 12.
Twelve, fourteen.
Uncle,
if you have any questions about the accounts,
feel free to ask me.
Otherwise, our agency
will suffer losses.
Round two.
Cheng Qi wins.
The score is
one to one.
It's just ten at most.
What a shame.
Round three.
Both brave and wise.
What's the most important thing
in escorting?
It's to judge the situation
and make wise decisions.
This round
is the final round.
The first to get the command flag
can choose who is Jiaojiao
among the five women at the finish line.
The one who chooses correctly
wins.
Dabao,
just do it.
Don't overdo it.
Okay.
Start the game.
Dabao,
fight hard.
If you win, you can see your mother.
If you lose,
no candy,
no food.
What are you daydreaming about?
Go get the command flag!
Dabao,
how much longer are you going to choose?
Are you waiting for the sun to set?
This is what you call being thoughtful.
Look at Dabao's deep affection.
He will definitely treat Miss Su well.
It's her.
She is my sister.
My sister smells nice.
I can smell it.
Come.
Girls from the music conservatory
have slender fingers.
Miss Su practices martial arts every day.
Her fingers must be rougher.
Grandfather,
Uncle,
Brother,
this is my wife, A Jiao.
We love each other
deeply.
No matter how many veils she has,
I can still recognize her.
Okay.
Since
you've all made your choice,
then
let's reveal the answer at the same time.
Let's unveil the veils together.
One,
two,
three.
Dabao,
Do I look pretty?
The competition is over.
From now on,
Cheng Qi is the son-in-law of the Su family.
You should take on the responsibility
of the escort agency together.
The point is
you can't let down
your parents
and me.
I can
Whether I have a son-in-law or not,
I can run this family well.
I won't let you down.
From now on,
don't worry about me.
Don't get the Escort Agency into trouble.
I'm doing this for your own good.
It's not necessary.
You...
There are new people in the family.
Everyone should behave.
Gong Xi, Fa Cai.
Grandfather.
Bring the things in.
Yes.
This is the ancestral heritage of the son-in-law of the Su family.
From today on,
I'll give it to you.
You should keep it well.
The key is
to use it well.
Use it well.
It's a legacy.
Better safe than sorry.
[The dowry I got.]
[So mysterious.]
[What's the great treasure?]
By the way,
I've turned that side room into a storage.
From today,
you can move into Jiaojiao's room.
No way.
It's fine. My room is spacious.
I mean, Yicheng has nowhere to stay.
It's okay, son-in-law.
There's an empty bed in our room.
You can stay.
Don't say I'm not generous.
How about we split it in half?
Since it's from my grandfather,
it's yours.
I don't want it.
Miss Su is so generous.
Then I won't be polite.
Armors.
It's old.
Knee pads.
That's my grandfather.
It's a legacy.
Better safe than sorry.
The Tale of the Su Son-in-law.
Don't dress in gaudy clothes.
Don't dress too revealingly.
Don't hide money.
Don't drink and carouse.
Don't be disloyal.
Don't be unfaithful.
What kind of family heirloom is this?
This is...
You have good writing skills.
I'll let you write it.
The last page of The Tale of the Su Son-in-law surprised me.
to be so serious.
Yes.
As you wish.
Divorce agreement.
I, Su Yuejiao,
and Cheng Qi,
are incompatible
and can't understand each other.
We are divorced.
From now on,
we are divorced.
We owe each other nothing.
Go our separate ways.
It should be
each find joy in their own way.
You stay in Yunjing
to prepare for the Nebula Assembly,
and bear the name of marrying into the Su family.
After a month,
when I get the escort seal,
and officially take over the family,
I'll give you the divorce agreement.
Then you won't be a matrilocal son-in-law.
But as long as you live in the escort agency,
feel free to ask me for help.
Miss Su,
I have a question
after these days.
I don't know if I should say it.
Say it.
There are your brother
and your uncle in the family.
Why do you have to be the head of the family?
Jiaojiao
grew up in the Escort Agency,
almost forgetting she's a woman.
Now that she's married,
someone can finally help her.
I don't recognize this brother-in-law.
He's too weak.
What's so great about him?
No one is good enough for my sister.
Are you suggesting she marry Zhen Dabao?
Look around the Agency,
who can truly help her?
Me,
or you?
I'll be a good assistant to Jiaojiao.
I'll take care of her.
I hope so.
You
shouldn't be around those pieces of wood all day,
or you'll become a blockhead.
Cheng Qi is a good man.
He's handsome,
considerate,
and knows when to advance and retreat.
He's better than your father.
Of course,
he's not as good as me when I was young.
He needs to be well trained.
I see, Grandpa.
I will definitely train him well.
I like being an escort.
Every time I successfully deliver the goods to the employer,
I feel very relieved.
As if I have fulfilled a certain trust.
and feel like a heroine.
I know.
If you like it,
you won't find it hard,
let alone
finding your value
in it.
What about you?
Your father is a great fighter,
yet you don't practice martial arts.
You want to attend the Nebula Assembly.
I'm not cut out for martial arts,
and I don't want to be an official.
But I love writing.
So I want to
win the most important poetry gathering in the Yun State.
I see.
It's late. Go to bed.
You...
Is this appropriate?
Chief Escort Su,
how can you let a woman sleep on the ground?
My father would kill me if he knew.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Go to bed now.
Why can't a woman sleep on the ground?
It's really strange.
What's that?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I almost died.
It's still dark outside.
You didn't even light the lamp.
Are you going to be a thief?
We've always been training in Yin hour.
I don't need to light the lamp.
Yin hour?
Then I need to sleep more.
One,
two,
three,
four.
Let's start over.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Military Aristocratic Family.
Defending the country.
Guarding a region.
Keep your arms flat and don't shake.
Don't shake.
Flat, shake.
Squat, squat, squat lower.
Military Aristocratic Family.
Squat down.
Guard a place.
Military Aristocratic Family.
Defend the country.
No talking.
Sleep on the ground.
You are sensible.
Otherwise,
you would have died.
Understand?
Cheng Qi
didn't take the exam.
Maybe it's because he's just a son of a county sheriff.
He doesn't have much chance to get a scholarly honor.
He's a live-in son-in-law in Su's Escort Agency.
So he can only sponge off his wife.
Not bad.
Miss.
Not bad?
I like his family background.
is just what I'm looking for.
Go ahead and post the notice.
Yes, my lady.
My brother has been here.
Drink the ginger soup after breakfast.
It's so complicated.
I guess we can only smash it open.
Your brother said
if this door is smashed,
I'll be dead.
Wait for me to finish eating before you smash it.
It's not that serious.
You'd better take care of yourself.
Don't go!
Brother, it's not me.
Help!
Chief Su almost quarreled with her uncle
because of the breakfast.
That's too much.
They can even quarrel over breakfast.
Escorts eat only after morning drills.
Chief Su knows you caught a cold last night,
so she made an exception.
She's so sweet.
You didn't see her running out of the room.
She left me alone.
Fortunately, I had a full meal before being beaten.
Otherwise, no energy to squeeze in and see the list.
Come on.
Hurry.
Make way.
The talents on the list,
Miss is waiting for you.
Young Master, I'll wait for you outside.
What are you going to do?
I saw someone.
I have to go to her.
Is she a girl?
Go ahead.
Good morning.
You go early and come back late.
Stop.
It's really you.
Liar!
Give back the betrothal gifts of my master.
Who are you?
Don't talk nonsense.
Bullying a weak woman like me.
Half a month ago,
my master made an appointment with you
to get married here.
Help!
Help! He's kidnapping me!
Stop yelling!
How dare you make trouble
on my turf?
You said I lied to your master,
do you have any proof?
You were there that day,
come with me to the court!
You can even recognize me?
I don't have time for this!
No evidence or witness.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't go.
Your master has married someone else.
It's useless.
What?
You...
It's a scam.
Don't follow me.
Or I'll call the government office to arrest you.
You can't get your money back.
She probably
lost it in a gambling house.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
Are you two in this together?
Your master paid for a marriage,
he must have ulterior motives.
Even if we went to the authorities,
it wouldn't be clear.
I can't just let this go.
I...
Congratulations to all who passed the preliminary exam.
Next,
you have seven days to prepare for the second examination.
Please draw your own topic
from the lottery tube.
I look forward to your performance in seven days.
Young Master Cheng
Thank you.
Do you have any questions about the topic of the meeting?
No, no.
I just didn't sleep well last night.
I'm sorry.
If you need,
you can stay in the guest room of Huayue Tower.
It's quiet.
I don't want to stay outside.
Thank you for your kindness.
In that case,
please help yourself.
But
don't lose the forest for the trees
and delay the competition.
That's for sure.
I hope all of you
can bring glory to the Yun State.
Please prepare well
and make good use of your time.
Thank you for the advice.
He actually dared to refuse your kindness.
Should we teach him a lesson?
This uncultured country boy.
Let's see how he performs in the second examination.
I drew the word "win".
Brother Lin, you drew the word "tie".
Brother Lin, what's your take on this?
Since this is the grandest poetry event in Yunjing,
it must be selecting talents for the court.
They must want to see how we solve the problem.
How does the one who drew "win" go about winning?
How does the one who drew "lose" or "tie"
turn the tables to win?
Or perhaps,
They want to test our so-called desire for gain and loss.
You come from Ning'an County
and are not familiar with Yunjing City.
I heard that
the Grand Tutor will preside over the second examination.
Miss Zhang's design
is to test
ability and ambition
to select the pillar of the Yun State.
You're really amazing.
You're the best of the best.
What you said is what we are thinking.
No wonder, no wonder.
Good boy.
You develop so fast.
Young Master, she's a liar.
Yes, yes, yes.
Come to the Matchmaker Pavilion more often.
What are you going to do?
I'm afraid she'll run away.
You see, she's obviously playing hard to get.
You should
take it step by step.
Don't be in a hurry.
My wife.
I... I've told you
not to be in a hurry.
My wife.
Wait for me.
I'll go back with you.
Don't call me like that.
There are no family members here.
Do you want me to call you Chief Escort Su?
Acting should be rigorous.
Can you train after dawn?
I want to sleep longer.
I almost fell asleep
in the meeting.
The rules of the Escort Agency can't be changed.
Your rules.
So what?
I'll sleep in another room.
The warehouse is also fine.
It's full of stuff.
This won't do, that won't do.
Fine.
I can't live in this escort agency.
Don't move.
Su Lishi is watching.
I want to live in Huayue Tower.
I'll figure out a way.
Chief Escort Su agreed.
A promise made must be kept.
You're not my wife now.
My dear,
I'll accompany you to escort goods
whenever I'm free.
You won't be lonely.
Watch your steps. Don't look back.
One, two, one, two.